20somethingfinance.com 2012-06-20

# Privacy

20somethingfinance.com respects your privacy. We do not release your e-mail address to anyone or any company.

We may make content or services from other Web sites including our affiliated or co-branded Web sites available to you from links located on 20somethingfinance.com. These other Web sites are not subject to this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you review the privacy policy at each such Web site to determine how that site protects your privacy.

Following are the specifics of how we protect your privacy.

**WHEN YOU VISIT** 20somethingfinance.com. Our server automatically recognizes the IP address of visitors. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors and subscribers use and navigate our Web sites, including the number and frequency of visitors and subscribers to each Web page, and the length of their visits.. We share them with no one.

Like many other Web sites, 20somethingfinance.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**WHEN YOU FILL OUT A FORM ON** 20somethingfinance.com. When information is provided via feedback forms, we collect all of the information you provide, including your e-mail address and the type of browser being used. However, this information is not compiled or used for any purpose other than to communicate with you.

**COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS.** 20somethingfinance.com may place a “cookie” in a file on your computer. The cookie itself does not collect or reveal any personally identifying information about you. The company that serves ads on our Website uses cookies for various tracking purposes. You always have the option of disabling cookies via your browser preferences. 20somethingfinance.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**THIRD PARTY USE.** We use third parties, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to deliver ads to you on our behalf. They also may collect and use non-personally identifiable information about your visits to the Services and other Web sites in order to present advertisements that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice or to opt out of having this information used by third-party ad servers to provide targeted ads, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp>.For information about cookies from Google Analytics, visit [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/).

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on 20somethingfinance.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

20somethingfinance.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. 20somethingfinance.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**WHEN YOU CLICK ON A LINK TO ANOTHER WEB SITE.** This Web site contains links to other sites, including advertiser sites, and content partners. These sites are not under our control and so are not covered by our Privacy Policy statement. We recommend that you review the privacy policy at each such Web site to determine how that site protects your privacy.

**DOUBLECLICK DART COOKIE.**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on 20somethingfinance.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to 20somethingfinance.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/).

**WHEN YOU PARTICIPATE IN AN ONLINE SURVEY.** We may share survey information about our users with advertisers and business partners. However, we keep and share only aggregate numbers. For example, we will say x percent of our users are females and y percent males. We do not reveal any individual information about you.

**WHEN YOU SIGN UP FOR E-MAIL UPDATES AND COLUMNS.** 20somethingfinance.com promotions, as well as outside advertising, will appear on e-mail alerts. From time to time, 20somethingfinance.com may send you e-mail notifications about new or existing products and services, new web site features, special offers, or to otherwise contact you. Your e-mail address will not be released to other companies or organizations. You can remove your name from the e-mail subscription list at any time by using the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each of our e-mails.

*** YOUR ABILITY TO CHOOSE.** If you subscribe to an e-mail alert, you may update your communication preferences by visiting the feedburner opt out link in your email.

**WHEN YOU PARTICIPATE IN A FORUM.** You should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personal information (e.g., user name, e-mail address) in the forums or during a chat, that information can be collected and used by others not connected with 20somethingfinance.com, and may result in unsolicited messages from them.

**CHANGE OF OWNERSHIP** of 20somethingfinance.com. Some or all personal information maintained by 20somethingfinance.com may be subject to transfer to another company in the event of a change of ownership of 20somethingfinance.com or sale of any part of 20somethingfinance.com.

**POLICY MODIFICATIONS.** When we make any material change to this Privacy Policy, we will inform you by posting a notice on the home page of this site that the policy has been updated and by changing the date on this page noting when the policy was last updated.  
**  
EXCEPTIONAL CIRCUMSTANCES.** In addition to the above circumstance, we may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law, (ii) in response to legal process, (iii) to law enforcement authorities or other government officials, or (iv) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity.

**TERMS OF SERVICE:** For the 20somethingfinance.com terms of service, [click here](http://20somethingfinance.com/terms-of-use/).

**CONTACT:** If you have any questions, please contact us via the 20somethingfinance.com [contact form](http://20somethingfinance.com/contact/).

**LAST UPDATED:** February 2, 2010
